Citizens Environmental Coalition; Records apap197
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Issue Files, 1978-2002; 5; 10.73 cubic ft.
  - Mercury Contamination, 1986-1997 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 4)
  - Mining, 1992; 1995-2000; 2002 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 5)
  - MSDS, 1993 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 6)
  - Municipal Waste Incineration, 1978; 1987-1990 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 7)
  - Municipal Waste Incineration, 1991-1999 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 8)
  - Musicians, 1990-1991 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 9)
  - Natural Resource Damage, 1993-1995 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 10)
  - New York State DEC, Filled Positions by Funding Source, 1996 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 11)
  - Niagara Mohawk/Harbor Point Remediation Project, 1994-2000 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 12)
  - Noise Pollution, 1991; 1993; 1998; 2002 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 13)
  - "Non Point Source Management Program", NYSDEC, 2000 October (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 14)
  - Nuclear Power, 1978; 1988; 1991-1996; 1998 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 15)
  - Occupational Health Clinics, Undated (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 16)
  - Oil Spills, 1997; 1999-2000 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 17)
  - Oil Spills -- RBCA, 1996-1997 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 18)
  - Oil/Gas Drilling, 1991; 1994; 1996 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 19)
  - Oil/Gas Prevention, 1989-1990; 1992-1996; 2001 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 20)
  - Oil/Gas Prevention, 1992; 1994-1999; 2001 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 21)
  - On-site Environmental Monitors, 1992-1997 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 22)
  - Open Burning, of Garbage, 1988-1990 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 23)
  - Open Burning, of Garbage, 1991 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 24)
  - Open Burning, of Garbage, 1992 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 25)
  - Open Burning, of Garbage, 1993-1995 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 26)
  - "Organic Chemicals and Drinking Water", New York State Department of Health, 1980 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 27)
  - Organizations and Media Directories, 2002 (Box 7 (5-Issue Files), Folder 28)
  - Packaging Reduction Bill, The Environmentally Sound Packaging Act, 1993-1995 (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 1)
  - Pataki, 1995-1996; 1998 (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 2)
  - PCBs, 1984-2002 (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 3)
  - PCBs, 1984-2002 (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 4)
  - Permit Regulations, 1992-1996 (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 5)
  - Persistent Organic Pollutants (POPs), 1995-1996; 1998; 2000 (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 6)
  - Pesticide Harzards/Exposure, 1987-2001; 3 folders (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 7-9)
  - Plastics, 1990-1996; Undated (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 10)
  - Pollution Prevention/Toxics Use Reduction, 1987-1997 (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 11)
  - Precautionary Principle, 1998; 2001 (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 12)
  - Property Values and Toxics, 1991-1996 (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 13)
  - Public Authorities Control Board, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 14)
  - Public Speaking, 1982; 1989; Undated (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 15)
  - Radiation and Health, 1983-2000; 2 folders (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 16-17)
  - Radiation Standards, 1990-1996 (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 18)
  - Radio Ads, 1996-2001; 2 folders (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 19-20)
  - Radioactive Waste, High Level, 1981-1999 (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 21)
  - Radioactive Waste Incineration, 1986; Undated (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 22)
  - Radioactive Waste, Low Level, 1985-1999 (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 23)
  - Radon, 1988-2002 (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 24)
  - Regional Farm and Food Project, 1995-1999 (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 25)
  - Resource Conservation and Recover Act (RCRA), 1986-1998 (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 26)
  - Recycling, 1989-2003 (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 27)
  - Relocation, 1991; 1999 (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 28)
  - Reproductive Hazards, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 29)
  - Risk Assessment, 1991-1993 (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 30)
  - Risk Assessment, 1992 (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 31)
  - Risk Assessment, 1985; 1989; 1992-1999 (Box 8 (5-Issue Files), Folder 32)
  - Risk Based Corrective Action (RBCA), 1995-1996; 1998-1999 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 1)
  - Risk Communication, 1988-1995 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 2)
  - "Seminar Publication: Wellhead Protection: A Guide for Small Communities", EPA, 1993 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 3)
  - SEQRA, 1994-2001 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 4)
  - Sewage Sludge, EPA, 1991-1993; 1995-2000 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 5)
  - Sewage Sludge, National Sludge, 1980-1985; 1988-1989 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 6)
  - Sewage Sludge, National Sludge, 1990-1992 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 7)
  - Sewage Sludge, National Sludge, 1993 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 8)
  - Sewage Sludge, National Sludge, 1994-1996 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 9)
  - Sewage Sludge, National Sludge, 1997-1999; Undated (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 10)
  - Sewage Sludge, New York Sludge, 1988-1992 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 11)
  - Sewage Sludge, New York Sludge, 1993-1994 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 12)
  - Sewage Sludge, New York Sludge, 1995-1997 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 13)
  - Sewage Sludge, New York Sludge, 1998-1999; 2001; Undated (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 14)
  - Sewage Sludge, Organic Standards, 1979-1981; 1998 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 15)
  - Sewage Treatment, 1985; 1992; 1994 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 16)
  - Significant Threat, 1988; 1992; 1994 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 17)
  - Siting, 1992-1993; 1995 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 18)
  - Siting ("Cerrell" Report), 1984 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 19)
  - SLAPP's, Harassing Lawsuits, 1989; 1991 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 20)
  - Solid Waste Dumping, 1991; 1993; 1995-1996; 1999; 2001 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 21)
  - Solid Waste TAGM's, 1988-1991; 1994 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 22)
  - Solid Waste/Landfill Regulations, 1988-1989; 1991-1996; 1998; 2001 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 23)
  - SPDES, 1990-1991; 1993; 1996; 1998 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 24)
  - SSMB, 1986-2001 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 25)
  - Superfund/CERCLA, 1986-1992 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 26)
  - Superfund/CERCLA, 1995-1996 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 27)
  - Superfund/CERCLA, 1997-2002 (Box 9 (5-Issue Files), Folder 28)
  - TAGM's: Technical and Adinistrative Guidance Memoranda, 1988-1995; 2 folders (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 1-2)
  - TAG's: Technical Assistance Grants, 1987-1988; 1990; 1992-1994 (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 3)
  - Testing, Environmental, 1995; 1997-2000 (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 4)
  - Thermal Desorption, 1991-1994 (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 5)
  - Tire Recycling and Burning, 1991; 1995-1997; 2000 (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 6)
  - Toxics Release Inventory (TRI), 1999 (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 7)
  - Transportation, 1985-1986; 1989-1992; 1994 (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 8)
  - TRI: Toxic Release Industry, 1986; 1989; 1991; 1993; 1995 (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 9)
  - T-Shirts, 1995 (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 10)
  - Unions, 1990; 1993; 1995-1996 (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 11)
  - USGS United State Geological Services, 1991 (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 12)
  - Video Taping, 1991; 1993-1995 (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 13)
  - Voluntary Cleanup, 1994-1996 (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 14)
  - Voluntary Cleanup, 1994; 1996-1997; 2000 (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 15)
  - Waste Management, 1990-1992; 1996; 1998 (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 16)
  - Waste Management, 1987; 1990-1992; 1995-1999 (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 17)
  - "Waste Management, Inc.: A Corporate Profile", CCHW, 1988 (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 18)
  - "Waste Management, Inc.: An encyclopedia of Environmental Crimes and Other Misdeeds", 1991 (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 19)
  - "Waste Management, Inc.: Press Reports about Violations of Law", p. 1-120, 1988 (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 20)
  - "Waste Management, Inc.: Press Reports about Violations of Law", p. 121-240, 1988 (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 21)
  - "Waste Management, Inc.: Environmental Crimes and Misdeeds", Greenpeace, 1991 (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 22)
  - Water Management, DEC, 1996-1998 (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 23)
  - Water Pollution, Non-Point, 1988; 1992; 1994-1996 (Box 10 (5-Issue Files), Folder 24)
  - Water Testing, 1992-1993; 1997; 2000 (Box 11 (5-Issue Files), Folder 1)
  - Water Treatment, 1987-1991; 1993; 1995-1996 (Box 11 (5-Issue Files), Folder 2)
  - Watersheds, 1990; 1996; 1999 (Box 11 (5-Issue Files), Folder 3)
  - Whistleblowers, 1991-1992 (Box 11 (5-Issue Files), Folder 4)
  - Wood, 1997; 2000-2001 (Box 11 (5-Issue Files), Folder 5)
  - Worker Exposures, 1980; 1986; 1991; 1994 (Box 11 (5-Issue Files), Folder 6)
  - World Wildlife Fund, the Global Toxic Chemicals Initiative, 2002 (Box 11 (5-Issue Files), Folder 7)
  - Zero Discharge Alliance, 1990-1991; 1996 (Box 11 (5-Issue Files), Folder 8)
  - Asbestos, 1982-1997 (Box 12 (5-Issue Files), Folder 1)
  - Beneficial Use Determination (BUD), 1993-1997 (Box 12 (5-Issue Files), Folder 2)
  - Breast Cancer, 1991-1999 (Box 12 (5-Issue Files), Folder 3)
  - Cancer, 1977-1997 (Box 12 (5-Issue Files), Folder 4)
  - Construction and Demolition (C + D) Pollution, 1988-1998 (Box 12 (5-Issue Files), Folder 5)
  - Cost Benefit Analysis, Undated (Box 12 (5-Issue Files), Folder 6)
  - Integrated Waste Systems (IWS), 1991 (Box 12 (5-Issue Files), Folder 7)
  - Oil/Gas Spills, 1998 (Box 12 (5-Issue Files), Folder 8)
  - SPDES, 1996 (Box 12 (5-Issue Files), Folder 9)
  - Unions, Undated (Box 12 (5-Issue Files), Folder 10)
  - Waste Management, 1991-1992 (Box 12 (5-Issue Files), Folder 11)
- News Clippings, 1994-2000; 6; 1 cubic ft.
  This series consists of news clippings CEC took from newspapers and other publications about environmental issues and CEC activities.
  - Cancer, Nuclear Waste, 1996-2000 (Box 1 (6-News Clippings), Folder 1)
  - DEC, Earth Day, Environment, 1994-1999 (Box 1 (6-News Clippings), Folder 2)
  - General, 1987 (Box 1 (6-News Clippings), Folder 3)
  - General, 1988 (Box 1 (6-News Clippings), Folder 4)
  - General, 1989 (Box 1 (6-News Clippings), Folder 5)
  - General, 1990 (Box 1 (6-News Clippings), Folder 6)
  - General, 1991 (Box 1 (6-News Clippings), Folder 7)
  - General, 1992 (Box 1 (6-News Clippings), Folder 8)
  - General, 1993 (Box 1 (6-News Clippings), Folder 9)
  - General, 1994 (Box 1 (6-News Clippings), Folder 10)
  - General, 1995 (Box 1 (6-News Clippings), Folder 11)
  - General, 1996-1999 (Box 1 (6-News Clippings), Folder 12)
  - Governor Pataki, Bonds and Bills, 1995-1999 (Box 1 (6-News Clippings), Folder 13)
  - Kodak, 1994-1999 (Box 1 (6-News Clippings), Folder 14)
  - Landis Plastics Factory Accidents, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (6-News Clippings), Folder 15)
  - Love Canal, 1995-1999 (Box 1 (6-News Clippings), Folder 16)
  - Pollution, Damage and Clean-up, 1994-1999 (Box 1 (6-News Clippings), Folder 17)
  - Superfund, 1995-1999 (Box 1 (6-News Clippings), Folder 18)
  - Toxic Waste Sites, 1996-1999 (Box 1 (6-News Clippings), Folder 19)
- Publications, 1985-2001; 7; 1 cubic ft.
  This series contains CEC publications including reports, pamphlets, the newsletter Toxics in Your Community, as well as others.
  - CEC News Bulletin, 2001 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 1)
  - CEC Pamphlet, ca. 1998 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 2)
  - CEC Reports, 1990 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 3)
  - CEC Reports, Undated (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Citizen's Guides/Handbook, 1987; 1990; Undated (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 5)
  - No Time to Lose, A Critical Overview of the Super Slow State Superfund with Recommendations for Reform, 1990 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 6)
  - A Tarnished Image: The Eastman Kodak Performance Scorecard, 1998 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 7)
  - Tools for Action, Undated (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 8)
  - Toxics in Your Community, 1985 September 24 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 9)
  - Toxics in Your Community, 1986 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 10)
  - Toxics in Your Community, 1987 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 11)
  - Toxics in Your Community, 1988 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 12)
  - Toxics in Your Community, 1989 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 13)
  - Toxics in Your Community, 1990 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 14)
  - Toxics in Your Community, 1991 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 15)
  - Toxics in Your Community, 1992 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 16)
  - Toxics in Your Community, 1993 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 17)
  - Toxics in Your Community, 1994 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 18)
  - Toxics in Your Community, 1995 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 19)
  - Toxics in Your Community, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 20)
  - Toxics in Your Community, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 21)
  - Toxics in Your Community, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 22)
  - Toxics in Your Community, 2000-2001 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 23)
  - Where Can the Children Play? A Report on Long Island's Priority Environmental Hazards & A Directory of Long Island Environmental Organizations, 1993 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 24)
- Research Files, 1978-2001; 8; 4 cubic ft.
  This series consists of chemical fact sheets used by CEC for research and informational purposes.
  - Index, ca. 1990s (Box 1 (8-Research Files), Folder 1)
  - Abestos - Azodiisobutyronitrile, ca. 1978-2001 (Box 1 (8-Research Files), Folder 2)
  - Acephate - Adriamycin, ca. 1978-1999 (Box 1 (8-Research Files), Folder 3)
  - Alachlor - Aluminum Sulfate, ca. 1986-1999 (Box 1 (8-Research Files), Folder 4)
  - Amino - Amitrol, ca. 1978-1989 (Box 1 (8-Research Files), Folder 5)
  - Ammonia - Amyl, ca. 1978-1999 (Box 1 (8-Research Files), Folder 6)
  - Aniline - Argon, ca. 1978-1995 (Box 1 (8-Research Files), Folder 7)
  - Arsenic and AS Compounds, ca. 1985-2001 (Box 1 (8-Research Files), Folder 8)
  - Bacteria, ca. 1989 (Box 1 (8-Research Files), Folder 9)
  - Barium - Beryllium Nitrate, ca. 1978-1995 (Box 1 (8-Research Files), Folder 10)
  - Benzene, ca. 1987-1993 (Box 1 (8-Research Files), Folder 11)
  - Bis - Butoxyl, ca. 1978-1999 (Box 1 (8-Research Files), Folder 12)
  - Butyl - Butyric, ca. 1978-1986 (Box 1 (8-Research Files), Folder 13)
  - Cadmium, ca. 1978-1999 (Box 1 (8-Research Files), Folder 14)
  - Calcium, ca. 1978-1986 (Box 1 (8-Research Files), Folder 15)
  - Cam - CES, ca. 1978-1997 (Box 1 (8-Research Files), Folder 16)
  - Chlora - Chlori, ca. 1978-1999 (Box 1 (8-Research Files), Folder 17)
  - Chloroa - Chloroe, ca. 1978-1999 (Box 1 (8-Research Files), Folder 18)
  - Chloroform, ca. 1978-1997 (Box 1 (8-Research Files), Folder 19)
  - Chloromethyl - CHO, ca. 1978-1999 (Box 1 (8-Research Files), Folder 20)
  - Chromic - Chromium, ca. 1978-2001 (Box 1 (8-Research Files), Folder 21)
  - Chry - Cobalt, ca. 1978-1995 (Box 2 (8-Research Files), Folder 1)
  - Copper - Cupric, ca. 1978-1999 (Box 2 (8-Research Files), Folder 2)
  - Cy - Cypermethrin, ca. 1978-1997 (Box 2 (8-Research Files), Folder 3)
  - 2,4-D - Dibutylphosphate, ca. 1978-1999 (Box 2 (8-Research Files), Folder 4)
  - Dica - Dicy, ca. 1978-1999 (Box 2 (8-Research Files), Folder 5)
  - Dieldrin - Dimethylbenzidine, ca. 1978-2001 (Box 2 (8-Research Files), Folder 6)
  - Dimethylbutane/Dinitrotolvene, ca. 1978-2001 (Box 2 (8-Research Files), Folder 7)
  - Di-n-Octyl - Phthalate - Dolomite, ca. 1978-1999 (Box 2 (8-Research Files), Folder 8)
  - Dioxin, ca. 1988 (Box 2 (8-Research Files), Folder 9)
  - Endosulfan/Ethylbutyrate, ca. 1978-2001 (Box 2 (8-Research Files), Folder 10)
  - Ethyl - Chloride/Ethyl Trichloro-silane, ca. 1978-1999 (Box 2 (8-Research Files), Folder 11)
  - Fa - Furfuryl Alcohol, ca. 1978-1999 (Box 2 (8-Research Files), Folder 12)
  - Fluoride, ca. 1978-1996 (Box 2 (8-Research Files), Folder 13)
  - G, ca. 1978-1997 (Box 2 (8-Research Files), Folder 14)
  - Hafnium - Hydrolic Acid, ca. 1978-1999 (Box 2 (8-Research Files), Folder 15)
  - Heavy Metals, ca. 1988-1993 (Box 2 (8-Research Files), Folder 16)
  - Hydrogen/Hydroquinone, ca. 1978-1999 (Box 2 (8-Research Files), Folder 17)
  - Indene - Isopropyl Isocyanate, ca. 1978-1999 (Box 2 (8-Research Files), Folder 18)
  - Jet Fuels, ca. 1996-1999 (Box 2 (8-Research Files), Folder 19)
  - K, ca. 1978 (Box 3 (8-Research Files), Folder 1)
  - Lead, ca. 1984-1999 (Box 3 (8-Research Files), Folder 2)
  - Lindane - LPG, ca. 1978 (Box 3 (8-Research Files), Folder 3)
  - Magnesium - Manganese, ca. 1978-2001 (Box 3 (8-Research Files), Folder 4)
  - Mercury, ca. 1978-2003 (Box 3 (8-Research Files), Folder 5)
  - Methacrylic aid/methylaniline, ca. 1978-1995 (Box 3 (8-Research Files), Folder 6)
  - Methyl Bromide/Methyl Hydrazine, ca. 1978-2001 (Box 3 (8-Research Files), Folder 7)
  - Methyl Iodide/Metron Dazole, ca. 1978-1999 (Box 3 (8-Research Files), Folder 8)
  - Mica - My, ca. 1978-1995 (Box 3 (8-Research Files), Folder 9)
  - O, ca. 1978-1996 (Box 3 (8-Research Files), Folder 10)
  - Pancreatin - phenyl, ca. 1978-2001 (Box 3 (8-Research Files), Folder 12)
  - Pho - Plutonium, ca. 1978-1999 (Box 3 (8-Research Files), Folder 13)
  - Po, including PCBs, ca. 1978-2001 (Box 3 (8-Research Files), Folder 14)
  - Pr - Py, ca. 1978-2001 (Box 3 (8-Research Files), Folder 15)
  - Q, ca. 1978-1989 (Box 3 (8-Research Files), Folder 16)
  - R, ca. 1978-1999 (Box 4 (8-Research Files), Folder 1)
  - Saccharin/Sodium Aluminum Hydride, ca. 1978-1999 (Box 4 (8-Research Files), Folder 2)
  - Sodium Arsenate/Hypochlorite, ca. 1978-1989 (Box 4 (8-Research Files), Folder 3)
  - Sodium Lauryl Sulfate/Sulprofos, ca. 1978-1999 (Box 4 (8-Research Files), Folder 4)
  - Solvents, ca. 1989-1991 (Box 4 (8-Research Files), Folder 5)
  - Talc - Tet, ca. 1978-1999 (Box 4 (8-Research Files), Folder 6)
  - Th - To, ca. 1978-2001 (Box 4 (8-Research Files), Folder 7)
  - Tr, ca. 1978-1997 (Box 4 (8-Research Files), Folder 8)
  - Trichloroethane (TCA), ca. 1978-1999 (Box 4 (8-Research Files), Folder 9)
  - Trichloroethylene (TCE), ca. 1986-2003 (Box 4 (8-Research Files), Folder 10)
  - Ts - Tz, ca. 1978-1986 (Box 4 (8-Research Files), Folder 11)
  - U, V, ca. 1978-1997 (Box 4 (8-Research Files), Folder 12)
  - W, X, Y, Z, ca. 1978-1997 (Box 4 (8-Research Files), Folder 13)